THOMAS ARCHBOLD

32 Purbrook Estate, Tower Bridge Road, London, SE1 3BZ tomjarchbold@gmail.com \diamond +44 7837 674 419 \diamond tomarchbold.com

BACKGROUND

I am a Ph.D. student at King's College London where I am part of the Distributed Artificial Intelligence group. My research interests are in algorithmic game theory and mechanism design, as well as other areas of theoretical computer science such as algorithms and complexity theory.

EDUCATION

MPhil/Ph.D. Computer Science, King's College London

2020-2024 (expected)

Research interests: algorithmic game theory, mechanism design, theoretical computer science

Supervisor: Professor Carmine Ventre

MSc. Computer Science, University of Warwick

2019-2020

Classification: Distinction

Dissertation title: A Decentralised Peer-Prediction Market (awarded distinction)

BSc. (Hons) Computer Science, University of Warwick

2016-2019

Classification: 2-1

Dissertation title: An Educational Kernel for the Raspberry Pi (awarded first class)

EXPERIENCE

Graduate Teaching Assistant, King's College London

Jan 2021-present

- 6CCS3OME Optimization Methods

2020/21

Private Tutor Oct 2020-present

Tutor for GCSE Computer Science. Involves planning and delivering one-on-one lessons, delivering feedback, and collectively deciding on which topics to focus.

Software Graphics Engineer Intern, Imagination Technologies, Kings Langley

Jul 2019-Sep 2019

Worked as part of the PowerVR Vulkan driver team researching Google's ANGLE API, analysing its performance on the driver, and writing targeted OpenGLES and Vulkan programs to test different areas of its functionality.

Contributed code to the driver and was involved in weekly team meetings to discuss progress and plans for the coming week.

Bartender, At Your Service Event Planning, London

Sep 2016-May 2017

Worked as a regular bartender at the Royal Albert Hall and served as part of the floor staff at various other events.

POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILITY

Seminar Organiser, Distributed Artificial Intelligence group, King's College London

Jan 2021-present

Helped organise fortnightly seminar within the Distributed Artificial Intelligence research group, which involved contacting external speakers to present talks on their work.

Presenter, International Conference for Undergraduate Research 2018

Sep 2018

Presented an individual research project on "Cellular Automata and Computational Universality" at the ICUR.

Produced an introductory primer on cellular automata and their applications as well as software to visualise them.

Senior Vice Captain, Queen Elizabeth's School

Sep 2015-Jul 2016

One among a team of ten "senior prefects" responsible for organising and helping out at various school events.

LANGUAGES AND SKILLS

Programming Languages

C, C++, Python, Lisp, Java, Bash

Tools Pandas, Numpy, Sklearn, Keras, GDB, Valgrind, Git, LATEX

 ${\bf Languages} \hspace{1.5cm} {\rm French} \; ({\rm B2/upper} \; {\rm intermediate})$

Russian (B1/intermediate)

WIDER ACTIVITIES AND ACHIEVEMENTS

First XV Player of the Season, University of Warwick RFC

2019/20, 2018/19

UWRFC First XV, QE Boys Rugby First XV, QE Boys Cricket First XI

2016-20, 2014-16, 2015-16

Alto Saxophone, Grade 8

2013

REFERENCES

Available upon request